≪(麻弓)あいつ
汁だくで何やってんの？
Look at how he's dripping bodily fluids everywhere.
It's sweat!
Bodily Fluids
(宇佐)汗ッ
He's been standing erect this whole time.
Bodily Fluids
Erect
立ってるとも 字 違うけどな
Bodily Fluids
Erect
I'm standing up! Use the right word!
Bodily Fluids
Erect
バイトに行くまでに
まだ時間あるから ちょっと読書を
I have some time before I go to work, so I was doing some reading.
If you have time to read erotic novels, you should go climb a pole instead.
エロ小説 読む暇あんなら
登り棒でもしてこいよ
Hey, now. I happen to be very particular about climbing poles.
≪(シロ)登り棒のことなら
俺 うるさいよ
This isn't an erotic novel.
エロ小説じゃないっすよ
先輩に借りた面白い小説で…
It's a great book that I borrowed from Senpai.
Ah,
ほほう クソ暑いのに律ちゃんの
好きなガワで待ち伏せか
so you're waiting in this crazy heat to ambush
Rit-chan while wearing her favorite outfit?
Good for you. Keep releasing those fluids.
ご苦労さん 我慢の汁 出して
汗！
It's sweat!
だって もうすぐバイト辞めるから
アピールしとこうと
Well, I'll be quitting my job soon, so I thought I'd show off while I can.
Why don't you keep working?
続けりゃいいじゃん
バイト料も高めだろ？
The job pays well, doesn't it?
But I'm tired of being Freak Show.
でも変ショリは嫌なんで
変人とは距離を置きたいし
I want to stay away from weird people.
Are you still upset about what Hayashi did?
お前
まだ林のこと気にしてんのか？
別に
It's not...
おい 今 お前の
ﾙｰﾑﾒｰﾄが作ってるものを見ろ
Hey, look at what your roommate's making right now.
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Too late to escape.
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
今さらだろ
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
(シロ)エヘヘッ
何たるアホらしい絶望感
I feel so hopeless, it's almost idiotic.
I'm going now.
行ってきます
そうそう
Oh, yeah. Rit-chan went to the book store first thing this morning.
律ちゃんは 朝一で本屋に行ったぞ
一番先にそれを言え！
You should've told me that sooner!
Episode Ten
Let Them Be
<はあ バイトを続ける… か>
Temporary summer closure on the17 th,18 th, and19 th of August.
The main restaurant will stay open as usual.
Kawahana Rd. Guesthouse ( Apprentice Cafe)
Should I keep working here?
<仕事は 割と楽しいし>
The work is pretty fun,
<バイト仲間も慣れてみれば
案外 居心地が>
and now that I'm used to my coworkers, I'm actually pretty comfortable here.
あッ この本棚 どうしたんです？
(山本)姉小路君
Where'd the bookshelves come from?
Anekouji-kun!
The Madame had them sent over from England.
奥様が
英国から仕入れてくださったんだ
さあ 我らの学びやを
完成させようではないか
Let us build ourselves a place of learning!
(西園寺)直訳すると
ｵｰﾅｰがｱﾝﾃｨｰｸ店で買ったんだって
Translation:
The owner bought them from an antique store.
本 しまうの手伝って
Help us put the books away.
These are wonderful shelves. The ghost of an upper-class English lady dwells in them.
いい棚だよね
イギリスの上品な婦人が憑いてて
Why did I want to get comfortable here?!
<居心地がよくなって どうする俺>
<変ショリ まっしぐらじゃねえか
辞める 絶対辞める！>
I'm headed straight back to the Freak Show!
I'm quitting! I have to quit!
<もう
あんな報われないのはごめんだ>
I've had enough of thankless work like that.
<先輩の部屋にも
古い本 いっぱいあったっけ>
There were a lot of old books in Senpai's room, too.
<こんな本棚 先輩 喜びそう>
She'd probably be thrilled if she saw these bookshelves.
<今度
さりげなく誘ってみようかな>
Maybe I should invite her along sometime...
≪(西園寺)
オーナー もう本ないです
Owner,
we're out of books.
Oh, but there's still space.
≪(タエ)
あら 少し空いちゃったわね➡
古書で
ぎっしり埋めたかったんだけど
I was hoping to fill it with old books.
Ah, if only our village elder's study hadn't burned down...
New books would just look tacky.
新書じゃ 何か味気ないし➡
It happened the day after I left the village...
こだわりたいわ～
I'd much rather have them match...
Uh, in that case...
あの じゃあ…
(律)ただいま
≪(住子)ちょうどよかった➡
I'm home.
Oh, perfect timing.
古い本を
しばらく貸してくれないかって
They want to know if you can lend them some old books.
ほら 律ちゃんも
置き場所 困ってたでしょ➡
Weren't you saying you didn't have enough room for your books?
お礼に ｺｰﾋｰﾁｹｯﾄあげるって➡
They'll give us coffee tickets in return.
お店で本 読んできたら？➡
You can read at the café.
いっぱい本あるわよ
They have lots of books there.
いいな～
本 運ぶの手伝ってくれた人も
That sounds nice.
They'll offer cake to anyone who helps carry the books.
ケーキセットおごるって
やった～ 行く
Yay! I'm going!
≪(タエ)ありがとう
じゃあ待ってるわね
Thank you! We'll be waiting for you!
She agreed to lend some books.
貸してくれるって
Yes!
重いから シロ君が車で運ぶってさ
えッ シロさん 車持ってたんだ
They're heavy, so Shiro-kun will drive them over.
Drive? Shiro-san owns a vehicle?
Senpai is coming...
こっちの車かよ
This is the vehicle?
おお これだけの書物を
無償でくださるとは
You're willing to offer us all of these books at no cost?
恩に報いるよう しっかり読み込み
己の糧にせねば
You have our eternal gratitude.
We must read them well and let them nourish our minds!
You don't get to keep them.
And one day,
I will make it
to the capital...
And one day,
I will make it
to the capital...
(彩花)すご～い 彩花 子供で
本とかちょっと苦手だから
Amazing.
I always had trouble reading as a child.
真剣に読める人 尊敬しちゃう
I admire people who are serious about reading.
私も お前のどんな男でも
とりあえず粉かける所は尊敬する
And I admire your ability to immediately hit on
every man, no matter who he is.
幸せそう プルプルしてる
She looks so happy.
She's quivering.
先輩 紅茶
Senpai, here's your tea.
Oh, she's already absorbed.
<あッ もう入ってる>
<しょうがない人だな
でも何か>
There's no helping this girl...
But this is
<こういうの いいな>
kind of nice.
Shiro-san, what are you doing?
シロさん 何してるんすか？
いや～ 熱射病になりそうだなと
Oh, I think I'm about to get heat stroke...
You should get inside!
早く中に
このギリギリ感がたまらないよね
うまく干からびてくださいね
I love this borderline feeling!
Feel free to dry up and die, then!
あッ 霊感少女･林さん
Oh, it's Ghost Whisperer Hayashi-san!
≪(シロ)宇佐君に会いにきたんだ
So you're here to see Usa-kun?
(林)この前 ひどいことしたから
(シロ)うん あれはひどい➡
I was mean to him the other day.
Yeah, that was mean, all right.
That was some advanced abuse.
上級者向きだよ
(林)上級？
Advanced?
(林)どう謝っていいか…
I don't know how
to apologize...
(林)分かんない
俺 さっき
A few minutes ago,
I was enjoying a borderline heat stroke...
熱射病 ギリギリぜめやっててさ
おっと ドン引き ありがとう
Thanks for the creeped-out reaction!
宇佐君もドン引きで あきれて
Usa-kun was also completely disgusted.
こんなの置いてったよ どう思う？
But he left this here.
What do you think?
宇佐君の
変ショリ能力が進化してる
Usa-kun's Freak Show powers have evolved.
Oddhand Powers
It's impossible to not feel bad for him!
あっぱれな ふびんさだよね➡
林さんは？➡
What about you?
宇佐君は 君にどうだった？
How did Usa-kun treat you?
《<宇佐君 教室かな>》
Is Usa-kun in the classroom?
《<ネットで仕入れた
怖い話 しなきゃ>》
I have to tell him about the scary story I found on the Internet.
《<それと…>》
Plus...
《(女子Ａ)さっき 林がﾁｮｺっぽい袋
持ってんの見ちゃった》
Hey, guess what?
I just saw Hayashi carrying what looked like a bag with chocolate inside.
《(Ｂ)マジ？ 誰にあげんの あいつ
霊とか入ってそう》
Seriously? Who's she giving it to?
It's probably haunted.
《(Ａ)そりゃ 宇佐君っしょ》
Probably Usa-kun.
Ugh, I feel sorry for him.
《(Ｂ)うわッ 気の毒
でもさすが変人処理班》
But the Freak Show Ringmaster might get all emotional and date her.
《ほだされて付き合ったりして》
《≪(Ａ)ない
林の対処するときの宇佐君➡》
No way.
Usa-kun looks really uncomfortable when he's talking to Hayashi.
《メッチャ困った顔してんじゃん》
And the Ghost Whisperer has no idea!
《≪(Ｂ)それに気づかん霊感少女
痛いわ～》
That's gotta hurt.
If Usa-kun wasn't there to put up with her,
《≪(Ａ)宇佐君が相手して
なかったら確実にｲｼﾞﾒｺｰｽだよね》
she would totally be a target for bullies.
《≪(Ｂ)変ショリ君 大変➡》
Freak Show has it rough.
《帰り あそこ寄ってかない？》
《≪(Ａ)いいね》
Oh, let's stop by there on the way home.
Sounds good!
《林？ 何してんだ？》
Hayashi?
What are you doing?
《えっと…》
Uh...
《宇佐君に
新しい怖い話をしてあげようと》
I wanted...
t-to tell you about a new scary story I found.
《ほどほどにしてくれよ
俺 怖いの苦手》
Go easy on me.
I don't handle scary stuff well.
《女子には あんまり言うなよ》
And you shouldn't tell it to any of the girls.
《ほら 怖がるしさ》
It'll probably scare them.
<(林)恥ずかしくて めまいがした>
I was so embarrassed, I could barely stay upright...
I didn't want to remember it...
<思い出したくなくて でも>
But
<私は 宇佐君に…>
what I did to Usa-kun...
シロさん！ いい加減にしないと…
Shiro-san! That's enough already!
えッ 林？
Hayashi?
えッ？
林って…
Isn't Hayashi...
わ… 私
I-I...
私…
I...
<何だ？ 何だよ こいつ>
What?
Why's she here?
<今さら何を…>
What does she want now?
≪(林)ありがとう
Thank you!
ありがとう 宇佐君
Thank you, Usa-kun,
無視しないでくれて
for not ignoring me!
気遣ってくれて➡
For being concerned about me
我慢してくれて ありがとう
and putting up with me...
Thank you!
甘えて ごめんなさい
I'm sorry I took advantage of you!
ありがとう
Thank you!
ひどいこと言って
ホントにごめん ごめん…
I'm really sorry about the mean things I said!
I'm sorry!
分かった もういいよ
I get it. It's okay.
ブハッ すっげえ顔
Your face is a mess.
ギャ～ッ
ウォータープルーフどこ行った➡
Isn't this supposed to be waterproof?!
ト… トイレどこ？
Wh-Where's the restroom?!
…ったく アホ宇佐 クソ甘えぞ
Man, stupid Usa.
You're too nice.
マスカラも
計算してやってたらいいのに
She should have messed up her mascara on purpose.
You're too easy. Isn't he, Rit-chan?
甘えよ なあ律ちゃん
<さすが先輩 まったくブレねえ>
Typical Senpai. Nothing can distract her.
林 とりあえず店入れよ
お前 シロよりＭなんじゃねえ？
Hayashi, why don't you come inside the café?
You're a bigger masochist than Shiro.
宇佐君さ 人が良すぎるよ
Usa-kun...
You're too nice.
こんな簡単に許していいの？
How can you forgive me so easily?
でも あのとき助けてもらったから
Well, I did have people to help me out...
<わだかまりは
まったくないわけじゃないけど>
Though I'd be lying if I said I didn't harbor any ill feelings.
<あのとき
先輩が来てくれなかったら…>
If Senpai hadn't shown up when she did...
そこまでの
ダメージはなかったっつうか
so I wasn't hurt that badly.
I probably wouldn't have forgiven her.
だから あの人達にも感謝しろよ
So you should also thank them...
なんつって
Just a thought.
<あとで俺も
先輩にありがとうって言おう>
I'll say thank you to Senpai later, too.
何か…
You know...
フラれた姿 見ると励ましたくなる
けなしにきたのに
Seeing her after she's been rejected makes me want to cheer her up.
But I came here to make fun of her.
仲間っていいね
黙れ
Aren't kindred spirits great?
Shut up!
フラれてないもん
いやいや
I wasn't rejected.
Uh, but...
昔から 絶対そういう対象に
ならないの分かってるのに
I was never the type to fall in love
if I knew it wouldn't work out.
不毛な恋 しないもん
彼氏確率 高いとこ
手堅くいかないと
I only aim for guys I have a good chance with.
Whoa, whoa...
おいおい
だって
After all...
かわいくなったんだから
もったいないじゃん
I'm a lot cuter now! I don't want to waste that!
言うほど かわいくねえぞ
You're not as cute as you think.
Just because you were both born with better looks...
自分達が
ちょっと元がいいからって！
｢達｣は いらねえ
No "both" about it.
Women's Washroom
≪(西園寺)ああ いた➡
Oh, there you are.
これ 君のだろ？
This is yours, right?
ど… どうも
Th-Thank you.
君 せっかくいい
守護霊つけてるのに➡
You have such a wonderful guardian spirit.
あきれさせるような
つまらないことするなよ➡
You shouldn't do stupid things that upset it.
合コン帰りのときは
どこか いっちゃってたよ
It left you on your way back from that group date.
でも ありがとうは よかったよ➡
But that "thank you" was commendable.
守護霊を大切にね
You should take good care of your guardian spirit.
Ba-dump
え～ッ お前の
スイッチ分かんねえ
What?!
I don't get what turns you on!
そして
分かりたくもねえ
And I don't want to know!
何つう 励まし甲斐のない女だ
It was a waste of time to try to cheer her up!
Has a lot of issues with that statement,
like how she wasn't cheering her
up to begin with
≪(住子)あら お帰り
Oh, welcome home.
どうだった？ 雰囲気がいいから
読書がはかどったでしょ
How was it?
The café has a pleasant atmosphere, so you must've done a lot of reading.
そうでもなかった
Not really...
あら 読んだ本がハズレだったの？
Oh, did you pick a bad book?
あれ 先輩は？
さっきまで本 読んでたけど
Huh? Where's Senpai?
She was reading until just now,
お前のことなど歯牙にもかけず
帰った？
and didn't even notice your presence.
She left?
≪(彩花)脇目も振らず
Without even giving you a glance.
Can you cut out the whispered jabs?
先輩
Senpai.
Do you have a moment?
ちょっといいっすか
That part was hilarious!
…ってとこ すっげえ面白かった
ﾄﾘｯｸが ばかばかしくていいよね
I liked how the trick turned out to be something stupid.
Yeah, it was so elaborate for no reason!
そうそう 無駄に凝ってて
あッ これって何て読むんすか
況んや
How do you pronounce this?
"Furthermore."
What's it mean?
何それ
なおさらとか ましてやとか
In addition to, or on top of.
Sounds like a pretty intelligent word.
難しい言葉
何か賢そうっすね 使おっかな
Maybe I'll use it.
Huh?
あれ？ 何書いてんの？ 宇佐君
What are you writing, Usa-kun?
Your fantasies are so out of control that
妄想が高じて とうとう自分で
エロ小説 書き出したのか？
you're writing your own erotic novels now?
That's the kind of self-sufficient life I want.
憧れの
自給自足ライフ
Usa's first novel titled First Time.
宇佐大先生 処女作
｢筆おろし｣
Everything is brand new!
どこもかしこも新しいね
読書感想文ですよ
I'm writing a book review!
I'm writing a review of the book I borrowed from Senpai for my summer homework.
夏休みの宿題で
先輩に借りた本の感想を…
Oh,
ああ ｢俺の処女作｣って単語だけで
もう十分か
you're turned on after hearing the phrase "first time"?
If you were a car, you'd get incredible gas mileage.
お前
車なら燃費の良さで受賞ものだな
God, there's no talking to her.
やだ この人 話 通じない
Wait, if this conversation continues, Senpai will go—
<こんな会話してたら
先輩どっか行っちゃっ…>
nowhere.
And?
<てない
本の話だと食いつきいいな>
And?
She's all over any conversation about books.
The customers at the café love the books you sent.
店に置いてる先輩の本
お客さんに喜ばれてますよ
The café is a little strange, but a lot of the customers are big readers.
色物カフェだけど
読書家の人も多いんですよね
ふ～ん
<先輩 嬉しそう>
Senpai looks happy.
Even Hayashi was excited about there being first editions.
この間 林も やたら感動してたし
初版がどうたら…
Huh?
えッ？
林って まだ来てんの？
Hayashi is still visiting the café?
She said she likes the atmosphere and has been coming there a lot.
店の雰囲気が気に入ったとかで
ここんとこ ずっと
She was a big reader in middle school.
あいつ 中学んとき本好きだったし
She was serious?!
Is your Freak Show spirit kicking in again?
お前 また変ショリ魂が…
There's no such thing!
ないっすよ そんな魂
I'll be quitting that job soon anyway.
もうすぐバイト辞めるし
Whoa, I need to get going!
…って もう行かなきゃ
行ってきま～す
Bye!
Is Usa getting nicer and nicer?
宇佐 お人よし度 増してねえか
ハズレ
あいつ
I didn't win...
He won't be able to quit his job at this rate.
絶対バイト
辞めらんねえぜ
They need his Freak Show powers to manage that bunch of weirdos.
あんな濃いやつら
変ショリじゃなきゃ無理
I guess masochism is infectious when you live in the same room.
同じ部屋だと
Ｍって感染すんだな
What?
じゃあ今度は俺が宇佐君から
感染して さらなる高みへ？
Does that mean Usa-kun's going to infect me and I'll reach a whole new level?
Can you start by leaving this room
とりあえず
部屋から出てってください
and never coming back?
そして 出てこないでください
≪(千夏)シ～ロ君
Shiro-kun!
Chinatsu-chan?
≪(シロ)千夏ちゃん？
Haven't seen you in a while.
久しぶりだね どうしたの
What's up?
(千夏)ずっと遊んであげなかった
から 寂しがってるかな～って
I was wondering if you were lonely since
I haven't spent any time with you.
So I was going to let you do
だから 千夏の夏休みの工作を
作らせてあげようと思って
my summer project for me.
Thank you for the request!
ご注文 ありがとうございます
And you can also do my drills.
あとドリルもやらせてあげる
追加注文 いただきました
And there's yet another request!
Shiro's gas mileage is good enough to start an energy revolution.
シロの燃費も
エネルギー革命レベルだよな
But I have no materials or time.
(千夏)
とはいえ 材料も時間もないし➡
Mud?
泥？
Oh, is that your lunch?
ああ お前の昼飯か
えッ？
Oh, yeah, Mayumi-san.
そうだ 麻弓さん
破れたﾊﾟﾝﾃｨｰｽﾄｯｷﾝｸﾞちょうだい
Can you bring me some worn-out pantyhose?
Is that your dinner?
お前の晩飯か
Shiny Mud Balls
Shiny mud balls?
光る泥だんご？
Shiny Mud Balls
Those were all the rage at one point.
一時期 話題になったよな
The key is to polish the mud with pantyhose.
≪(ｼﾛ)ﾊﾟﾝﾃｨｰｽﾄｯｷﾝｸﾞで
磨くといいんだって
I wanna try it!
<律ちゃんって
意外とこういうの好きだよな>
Rit-chan likes this kind of stuff more than you'd expect.
Well, it can't hurt to go back to being a child now and then.
まッ たまには
童心に帰るのもいいかもな
Being surrounded by shiny things can only be good.
光る玉なんて ちょっと縁起いいし
Like marrying into money.
玉のこし的な意味で
帰ってない
No child thinks that.
I'll make the shiniest ball!
一番きれいな玉 作ってやる
Since you're the oldest one here.
最年長らしく
うるせえッ
Shut up!
First, squeeze the water out of the mud
(シロ)まずは 泥をギュッと握り
水分しぼってから丸める
before you form it into a ball.
What? Damn...
あれ？ クッソ～
I can't get it round.
うまく丸まんねえ ああッ
Once it's balled up, pour dry dirt on it,
(シロ)
丸まったら乾いた土をかけて➡
and rub gently to get rid of the excess dirt.
なでるように表面の砂を落とす
Damn, I pressed too hard.
うわッ クソ 力入れすぎた
Sounds just like what you do when you fall in love.
まるで麻弓さんの恋愛みたいだね
When you find a good target, you press too hard and leave a mess.
いい玉狙うと力入りすぎて
おじゃん的な なんちゃって➡
Just kidding.
おわッ
This is weird...
おっかしいな 玉 転がすのうまい
ってよく言われんだけど
A lot of people have told me I'm good at rolling balls.
Lots of people praised me at my school's ball rolling event, too.
千夏も運動会で褒められたよ
大玉転がし
すっごく大きかったんだから
It was a huge ball!
ふ～ん 夜の運動会は割と小玉だぞ
Nighttime exercise usually involves smaller balls.
I'm also good at getting the balls into the basket.
玉入れも得意だよ
アハハ 玉は入んねえな
Nah, the balls don't fit.
When Usa-kun isn't here, everything gets out of control.
<宇佐君がいないと
流しっぱなしだな>
Mayumi
Ritsu
Chinatsu
Shiro
Once the balls are nice and round,
≪(シロ)きれいな球状になったら
ラップに包んで しばらく放置
wrap them up and let them sit for a while.
Thank you for the meal!
≪(千夏)ごちそうさまでした➡
Is Sumiko-san out?
住子さんは お出かけ？
友達のとこ行くって言ってた
She said she was going out to see a friend.
What about Usa-kun and Sayaka-san?
(千夏)宇佐君と彩花さんは？
宇佐君はバイト
Usa-kun's working.
Sayaka-chan went back home, I think?
彩花ちゃんは実家だっけ？
どうせ男じゃねえの
She probably found a man.
A date with her boyfriend? That sounds great!
彼氏とデート？
いいな～
Loves talking about love
No, she doesn't have a boyfriend. She just goes from one man to the next.
あいつのは彼氏じゃなく ﾌﾗﾌﾗと…
≪(千夏)ﾓﾃるんだ
So she's really popular!
No, I'm more popular.
違えよ モテるっつったら私の方が
あッ…➡
Mayumi-san, your ball cracked.
麻弓さんの玉 割れてる
えッ
Sob
Rub fine sand over the surface, and they're almost done!
(シロ)細かい砂を表面にすり込み
いよいよ大詰め
You can have the one I made for Shiro-kun.
シロ君に作らせてた分 あげるよ
(シロ)えッ 初耳
Huh? I didn't know about this...
Next, the moment you've waited for:
次は お待ちかね
ﾊﾟﾝﾃｨｰｽﾄｯｷﾝｸﾞで磨いて光らせます
Polishing them with pantyhose until they shine!
If you don't have pantyhose, you can use tracksuits
ﾊﾟﾝﾃｨｰｽﾄｯｷﾝｸﾞ以外にｼﾞｬｰｼﾞ
ﾚｼﾞ袋でもいいらしいよ
or reusable grocery bags instead!
It's incredibly disgusting how you refuse to call them "stockings" or "hose."
パンストとか略さない熱意が
心底 気持ち悪い
おお 光ってきた
Ooh, it's getting shiny!
A date, huh...
デートか～
Glance.
チラ チラ
What a nice ball.
いい玉だ
Loner-senpai, why don't you go on a date with Usa-kun?
ぼっち先輩は
宇佐君とデートしないの？
A date?! Wh-Why?
デ…？ な な 何で？
Hey, why was I ignored?
Aren't you a couple?
おい 何で飛ばした？
No.
Even though you live together?
Why did you ignore me?
何で飛ばした？
Don't put it that way.
In TV shows, couples get together just by seeing fireworks.
≪(千夏)ドラマとかだと
花火あたりでくっつく
We haven't seen fireworks.
花火 行ってないし
≪(千夏)そういうことじゃなくて
That's not my point.
Neither of us is interested in a relationship!
お互い そんな気ないのに
≪(千夏)そうなの？➡
Really? That can't be true about Usa-kun.
でも 宇佐君は違うっしょ➡
I'm positive that he likes you.
宇佐君は
先輩のこと絶対好きだと思うよ➡
Because he was really worried about you.
だって 先輩のこと気にしてたし…
I'm really sharp when it comes to that stuff.
千夏 そういうの鋭いんだよね
Sh-She said it!
い… 言ってもうた あっさり
Just like that!
Even Sayaka has never come out and said the words...
彩花ですら
律ちゃん相手に明言してないのに
Sadistic grade school girls are scary!
ＳＪＳ怖え
You're wrong.
それ違うよ
うん？
Usa-kun is just
宇佐君は 何ていうか
used to taking care of
ちょっと外れた人達の
people who are a little strange.
世話焼くことに慣れてるだけ
He could leave them alone, but he doesn't.
ほっとけばいいのに
ほっとかなくて
Instead, he takes care of them.
気にして 世話焼いて
That's normal for Usa-kun,
そういうのが
宇佐君にとって当たり前で
since he's so nice.
ものすごく お人よしで
He helps strange people so much, he's nicknamed Freak Show.
変人処理って あだ名が
つくづくピッタリで
I'm not special to him or anything.
だから
特別私がどうってわけじゃないよ
<律ちゃん…>
Rit-chan...
You're such a pain!
<めんどくせえ｢私に気があるんだ｣
で いいじゃねえか>
Just accept that he likes you!
He's so obvious about it.
Sayaka was right! She's living in her own world!
She worries too much about other people's feelings.
<人の心情とか考えすぎちゃうの
文系だから？>
Is it because she's big on reading?
What? Are you sure?
え～ッ そうかな？
I guess I wouldn't know the details.
まあ 千夏 よく知らないけど
That's right.
そうだよ バイト先でも
同中の女子 世話してるし
He's taking care of another girl where he works.
Oh, so you were just jealous.
な～んだ ぼっち先輩
ヤキモチ焼いてんだ
Wh-What?!
In other words, you're mad because
他の子にも同じように
優しくしてムカついたんだよね？
he's just as nice to other girls.
I never said anything of the sort.
さっきの会話に そんな要… ない
So what would you do if Usa-kun and I started dating?
じゃあさ 宇佐君と千夏が
付き合っちゃったらどうする？
通報する 宇佐君を
Call the police on Usa-kun.
Then what if he dated Mayumi-san?
≪(千夏)麻弓さんと
付き合っちゃったら？
Call the police on Mayumi-san.
通報する 麻弓さんを
Jeez, you're so stubborn.
≪(千夏)もう意地っ張りだな
Hey, cut it out.
おい もうやめろよ
人の気持ちを考えろ
Think of how other people feel.
つつかれたせいで
変に意識しちゃって
If you make her weirdly conscious of it by pushing her
and this turns into a sappy teen rom-com, I won't be laughing!
モジモジ青春ラブコメ突入とか
冗談じゃねえぞ マジやめろ
So stop!
私の気持ちを
考えろってことだよね
So you want her to consider how you feel!
You're outta here!
行ってらっしゃい
Hey, hey.
ねえ ねえったら ねえねえ
Hey, come on.
I'm home.
ただいま～
Huh? Chinatsu-chan?
あれ？ 千夏ちゃん？
Long time no see...
久しぶり
<Ｓっ娘が 何かおとなしい>
The sadist girl seems awfully quiet...
宇佐 今日も林 来てた？
Usa, was Hayashi there today?
She was.
来てましたよ
暇なんすかねえ それが？
She must be bored lately.
What about it?
Well, see, Rit-chan...
あッ いや 律ちゃんがな
えッ？
Senpai, is something bothering you?
先輩 何か気になることでも？
ああ…
別に
Not at all.
先輩？
Senpai?
What? Why?!
何？ 何で？ 何してたんですか？
What happened?
Oh, there was some ball rubbing and
≪(シロ)
ああ ちょっと玉さすったり➡
ﾊﾟﾝﾃｨｰｽﾄｯｷﾝｸﾞ破いて
しごいたりしてて…
pantyhose ripping going on.
Okay, what happened here?!
ホントに何してんだ！
Too bad for you, Usa.
残念だったな 宇佐
If you had come back an hour earlier,
お前が あと１時間早かったら
赤面･律ちゃんと青春できたかも
you could've enjoyed your youth with a blushing Rit-chan.
Once you grow up, you forget a lot of things.
大人になると色々 忘れてるよな
久々に思い出したよ
This was a good reminder.
Girls in grade school get so blindly
恋バナに
やたら食いつく女子小学生の
You like that
boy, right?
excited about love, it's beyond annoying!
We can
tell.
空気まるで読まない うっとうしさ
He's
here!
It makes you so mad, you even get sick of the guy the rumor was about.
ぶち切れて 噂の相手まで
嫌になっちゃうレベルの
Talk to him!
Hey!
I pushed her too hard. Tee-hee.
いじりすぎちゃった
I never knew it felt so good to watch someone else
自分の手を汚さず 青春消滅すると
あとで むなしくなくて
have their youth ruined without getting my own hands dirty!
すがすがしい気持ちになるな
I'm home. Oh, I haven't seen you in a while.
≪(住子)
ただいま あら 久しぶりね
You smell good, Sumiko-san!
≪(千夏)住子さん いい匂いする
Yes, see?
≪(住子)ああ これね
お友達に飾りパン習ってたの➡
My friend is learning how to bake decorative bread.
She said it'll last about a year.
１年くらい もつんだって
(千夏)かわいい
It's so cute!
She gave me the leftover dough, so would you like to make one?
余った生地もらってきたから
作ってみる？
It's fun, like playing with clay.
粘土遊びみたいで楽しいわよ
すぐできるし
And it doesn't take long.
I wanna try!
やる！ そんで これ工作にする
This can be my summer homework!
よく考えたら
泥だんごとか旬すぎてるし
On second thought, shiny mud balls are a thing of the past.
And they aren't cute.
かわいさに欠けるし
I accept your cut-and-run with pleasure!
斬り捨て御免 喜んで
Broken
Hey, what happened?!
ねえ 何があったの？
I barely got to show up in the second half and I'm left in the dark!
後半 出番少ないのに
何だこれ ひどい！
That's cold!
A
We'll
all
stay
pitiful
tomorrow
shi
ta
mo
bo
ku
ra
wa
mi
n
na
ka
wa
i
so
u
A
Preview
Sayaka-san's friend is coming to visit the Kawai Complex?
彩花さんのお友達が河合荘に？
(彩花)中学の同級生だよ
She was just a classmate in middle school, actually.
I didn't think Sayaka-chan had any female friends.
(シロ)女の子の友達って意外
(彩花)そうかな
Really?
Don't play coy.
よく言うよ 女が選ぶ嫌いな女
10年連続ナンバーワンのくせに
You've won the Woman-Other-Women-Hate Award ten years in a row.
I'm gonna squeeze your boobs later.
Now that I think about it, I haven't heard any of you talk about friends.
麻弓さんやシロさんも
友達の話 しない
A single man's best friend is his right hand and the amazing technique of—
(シロ)独身男性の最高の友は
いつも…
それ以上は
番組の存続に関わるのでやめて
You're going to get this show pulled off the air if you don't stop!
Well, friends would just be a pain, so I don't need any.
友達なんて いたらいたでウザいし
必要ないというか…
Episode Eleven
I Don't Have Any Friends
You shouldn't make fun of Senpai for being a loner, then.
先輩のこと
ぼっちとかバカにできないんじゃ
I'm always alone, but I'm not a loner.
That's right!